<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Summer Tango Camp Kolasin</string>

    <string name="notifications">Notifications</string>
    <string name="camp_guide">Camp Guide</string>
    <string name="food">Food</string>
    <string name="gallery">Gallery</string>
    <string name="contact">Contact</string>
    <string name="transport">Transportation</string>
    <string name="accommodation">Accommodation</string>

    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>

    <string name="action_example">Example action</string>

    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="title_activity_main_tab">MainTabActivity</string>

    <string name="hello_world">Hello world!</string>

    <string name="transport_guide_html">
<![CDATA[
<p class="P7"><span class="T1">BUS TIME TABLE</span></p><p class="P2"> </p><p class="Standard"><span class="T3">Bus  Station  Kolašin</span></p><p class="Standard"><span class="T3">Tel. + 382 ( 0 ) 20  864- 033</span></p><p class="P3"> </p><p class="P3">Beograd – Kolasin</p><p class="P3"> </p><p class="P3">7:00, 8:30, 12:30, 18:45, 19:00, 21:00</p><p class="P3"> </p><p class="P3">Kolašin – Mojkovac    ( Nacionalni park Biogradska gora ) </p><p class="P3">8:15,  8:20,  9:45,  10:30,  12:50 , 14:30,  15:40 , 16:50,  18:30</p><p class="P3"> </p><p class="P3">                                 </p><p class="P3">Kolašin - Bijelo Polje</p><p class="P3">8:30,  14:30</p><p class="P3">  </p><p class="P3">Kolašin - Berane</p><p class="P3">9:45,  10:30 , 14:30,  15:40, 16:50,  18:30</p><p class="P3"> </p><p class="P3">Kolašin - Andrijevica</p><p class="P3">9:45,  10:30,  14:45 , 16:50,  18:30</p><p class="P3"> </p><p class="P3">Kolašin  - Beograd</p><p class="P3">     12:20 </p><p class="P3"> </p><p class="P3">Kolašin - Podgorica</p><p class="P3">6:00, 8:00, 8:30, 9:40, 10:30, 11:00, 11:45, 12:45, 13:20, 14:10, 14:10, 14:50, 15:50, 16:30, 18:15</p><p class="P3"> </p><p class="P3">Kolašin - Pljevlja</p><p class="P3">8:45 , 12:45,  16:00</p><p class="P3"> </p><p class="P3">Kolašin  - Plav </p><p class="P3">9:40,  14:40,  16:50,  18:30</p><p class="P3"> </p><p class="P3">Kolašin - Bar     </p><p class="P3">6:00    </p><p class="P3"> </p><p class="P3">Kolašin-Budva</p><p class="P3">8:00, 14:10, 15:50, 16:30</p><p class="P3"> </p><p class="P3">Kolašin - Herceg Novi</p><p class="P3">8:00,  15:50,  16:30</p><p class="P3"> </p><p class="P3"> </p><p class="P3">                                             </p><p class="Standard"><span class="T2"> </span><span class="T3">Vozni red  – Railway station - Timetable</span></p><p class="P4">                                                TEL: + 382 ( 0 ) 441-492</p><p class="P5">VREME DOLAZKA  VOZOVA  U STANICU KOLAŠIN</p><p class="P1">Time of arrivals in Kolasin:</p><p class="P3">                                       </p><p class="P6">7:55                   BAR – BIJELO POLJE</p><p class="P6">8:20                   SUBOTICA – BAR</p><p class="P6">9:50                   BIJELO POLJE – BAR</p><p class="P6">11:20                 BAR – BEOGRAD</p><p class="P6">17:20                 BAR – BIJELO POLJE</p><p class="P5">18:05                 BEOGRAD (9:10) – BAR</p><p class="P5">05:03                 BEOGRAD (20:10) - BAR</p><p class="P6">19:25                 BIJELO POLJE – BAR</p><p class="P6">19:25                 BAR - SUBOTICA</p><p class="P6"> </p><p class="P3"> </p> <p class="P3"><span class="T1">TAXI SERVICE</span></p><p class="P1"/><p class="P2"><span class="T2">Mico Bulatovic              +38267 594 547</span></p><p class="P2">Bojić Rade                +382.69.548.488</p><p class="P2">Vlahović Veselin     +382.69.033.940</p><p class="P2">Vlahović Dragan     +382.69.662.244</p><p class="P2">Grujić Grujica          +382.67.508.935</p><p class="P2">Dožić Zoran             +382.67.537.738</p><p class="P2">Ivković Mladen       +382.67.537.784</p><p class="P2">Janković Manojle  +382.69.645.040</p><p class="P2">Rakočević Boro      +382.69.247.404</p><p class="P2">Radović Nebojša    +382.69.065.848</p><p class="P2">Čobeljić Velizar      +382.69.456.899</p><p class="P2">Šuković Vlado         +382.69.552.887</p><p class="P2"><span class="T2">Vlado Vlahović     +38267401421</span></p><p class="P2">Šuković Radojica    +382.69.464.104</p><p class="P2">Udruženje/Association Slava Lux: 19501</p>
]]>
</string>


    <string name="camp_guide_html">
<![CDATA[

				  <p>Dear all :),</p>
<p>It seems that this year&#8217;s Kolasin tango camp will be full of fun, play and love, as well as many tango and nontango adventures. We have received a large number of registrations which makes it clear that this event has become a true tango Woodstock in the mountains :) We wrote the same thing last year. This year it is even more obvious!</p>
<p><strong>Accommodation</strong></p>
<p>All who have registered for the <strong>cheaper accommodation</strong> (this is accommodation of good quality for which we have arranged cheaper prices with the accommodation owners who wish to nurture long-term cooperation with the tango camp) can count on getting it, but we have to point out that in some cases, in coordination with you, perhaps we will have to deviate a little from the announced prices and adjust to the situation in the field. This happens rarely and the deviations are small, however it doesn’t hurt to announce such a possibility <img src="http://www.summertangocamp.com/wp-includes/images/smilies/icon_smile.gif" alt=":)" class="wp-smiley" /> </p>
<p>Please send your accommodation registrations to <a href="mailto:tangonaturalmontenegro@gmail.com">tangonaturalmontenegro@gmail.com</a> In the registration you should write:</p>
<ol>
<li>Dates of arrival and departure</li>
<li>Number of people</li>
<li>Upper limit regarding the price</li>
<li>Do you need internet</li>
<li>Telephone numbers of everyone in the group (for easier communication in case something needs to be urgently communicated)</li>
<li>Specific demands if they exist</li>
</ol>
<p>You can certainly count on receiving information regarding your accommodation on time. On time also means a few days before the beginning of the event. For easier making of accommodation combinations, it&#8217;s important for us to first receive all the applications, and then do the accommodation arrangements all at once. Considering it is much more feasible for us, when looking for accommodation we will give priority to those who register in clearly defined pairs and groups. In case you don’t have a group (and you don’t plan to be in a single bed room), we suggest that you try to find your roommates for the tango camp through Facebook. We will strive to create groups as well as accommodate those who register solo, but wish to be accommodated together with other people due to prices or any other reasons, however these are situations which can be very complex as everyone has their own dates of arrival and departure and sometimes it is not possible to make a good match… In any case, prices range from 10-14 euros for single bed rooms, 8-10 for double rooms, 7-8 for triple bed rooms, and 6-7 for those with more beds. These are the prices in case you are staying for a minimum of 5 days. All who register before July 10 with clearly formed groups and clear demands regarding accommodation, we guarantee that they will receive adequate accommodation. Everyone else can count on our help, but not a guarantee, in finding accommodation. Another way to look for accommodation is through the website <a href="http://www.booking.com/">www.booking.com</a></p>
<p><strong>Camp schedule </strong></p>
<p>A lot of you, who weren&#8217;t here last year, have asked about the <strong>schedule of activities</strong>. A completely accurate schedule is not possible nor will it ever become possible <img src="http://www.summertangocamp.com/wp-includes/images/smilies/icon_smile.gif" alt=":)" class="wp-smiley" />  as this is an event in the mountains which are strange and unpredictable, and one rainy or windy day can turn the whole day around. In any case, along with many different tango activities, there will be many more other activities that Kolasin and primarily its surroundings offer, so that all who come to the camp, based on the number of days they stay, will have a chance to experience a truly broad range of activities. Even those who come for, say, three days can count on a wealth of activities, while those who only drop by can also count on a nice experience <img src="http://www.summertangocamp.com/wp-includes/images/smilies/icon_smile.gif" alt=":)" class="wp-smiley" /> </p>
<p>Also, as a less formal event, the Kolasin tango camp opens a lot of possibilities for <strong>initiatives</strong> by all the participants that will contribute to an even more fun time for everyone. You can see us as organizers who will do our best to make you feel comfortable, but even more as coordinators of a big tango hangout which will change, sometimes in the moment, based on the needs and desires of the participants, of course if the technical possibilities allow it. It shouldn&#8217;t be forgotten that this is an almost free event which practically doesn&#8217;t have a budget and which is organized by people who will do all of it (except some specific tours in the mountains etc.) on a voluntary basis.</p>
<p><strong>REGISTRATION PROCESS AND INFO DESK</strong></p>
<p>All camp participants should first sign in at the info and registration desk at Spomen dom upon their arrival to Kolasin, in order to take care of the obligation called &#8220;Two euros per day&#8221; <img src="http://www.summertangocamp.com/wp-includes/images/smilies/icon_smile.gif" alt=":)" class="wp-smiley" />  By this we mean the number of days in which you will take part in the camp&#8217;s activities. For instance, when you come in the morning, sleep over and stay until the evening, we count this as two days, i.e. four euros. So, you will tell us right away how much you&#8217;re planning to stay, we will sign you into the camp book, you will receive your &#8220;camp card&#8221; and you will pay your support to the event. Here you will also be able to ask everything you&#8217;re interested in, then and at any point during the camp, and we will try to have as many ready answers as possible :) Here we will also publish the schedule of activities for the next 1 to 3 days. <strong>You will pay for the accommodation</strong> either directly to the apartment owners or to us, but only when the owners are not in Kolasin, so that such an arrangement had been previously made. At the info desk you will also find offers of local agencies which organize other activities, so you can inform yourself here about them as well.</p>
<p>Here are the planned activities so far:</p>
<p><strong>Tango activities:</strong></p>
<p>Tango activities will be organized in three locations: Culture Center of Kolasin, Spomen dom (building of the assembly of Kolasin municipality) and Elementary school “Risto Manojlovic”. The frist two objects are found at Donji trg (the main town square), while the third is very near Donji trg.  This year the morning activities will take place in the mentioned elementary school which offers better conditions than the Culture Center, while the afternoon activities will be both in the first location as well as Spomen dom. We will use the Culture Center only in case there is a need for a third location.</p>
<ol>
<li>Classes &#8211; the idea is that classes will be mostly organized in the afternoon. The class topics, names of instructors and their level will be announced one, two or three days before on the info board at the info desk in Spomen dom. The classes will be held by instructors from Tango Natural, as well as other instructors from the region and Europe who are in that moment present in the camp.<br />
The frequency of the classes will depend on the current structure of the visitors and other activities that can be tiring – for instance, an entire-day mountaineering tour <img src="http://www.summertangocamp.com/wp-includes/images/smilies/icon_smile.gif" alt=":)" class="wp-smiley" />  Considering that this year we will have more locations for classes you can count on us making an even better distinction between levels so that the classes are not very crowded <img src="http://www.summertangocamp.com/wp-includes/images/smilies/icon_smile.gif" alt=":)" class="wp-smiley" /> </li>
<li>Practicas &#8211; our goal is for the camp to have a high level of interaction and exchange of knowledge so that all those present will take back home, apart from some wonderful memories, lots of new knowledge as well. A large part of the practicas will be either guided or monitored by instructors. Practicas will take place in the first half of the day in the elementary school (when there are no classes scheduled), as well as some afternoons in this location, as well as in Spomen Dom. Depending on the situation, the gatherings might sometimes spontaneously turn from a practica into a daily milonga. The same goes for the evening practicas. So, some activities will be strictly announced, while some will be coordinated based on the number of people and general level of energy.</li>
<li>Milongas – Last year due to the large number of visitors we had milongas almost every night  even though some of them started as practicas or practicalongas… Considering the number of those who’ve registered, it is certain that this year we will have the same situation. Music at the milongas will be played by DJs who are at that moment in the camp. Their names will be announced 1-3 days ahead.<br />
You can count on milongas in the open (outside) as well! Milongas on the town square with the performance of Tanguango, as well as milongas in the garden of Ski center “Kolasin 1450” are something we can guarantee <img src="http://www.summertangocamp.com/wp-includes/images/smilies/icon_smile.gif" alt=":)" class="wp-smiley" /> </li>
<li>Video projections and discussions &#8211; just like last year, this year we will relatively frequently organize video projections on the subject of Argentine tango. This includes both video clips of performances and other content related to tango culture, with commentary by the clip curators, as well as movies with a tango thematic.</li>
</ol>
<p>Apart from this we will also try to organize gatherings in a relaxed atmosphere &#8211; discussions in which the more experienced tangueros can share their experience and knowledge related to tango as a culture and dance.</p>
<p>We emphasize that there is a possibility that the mentioned locations will not be open all the time and available for dancing in situations when we estimate that too few people have the strength and will to dance :) - for instance, if all participants were in a intensive mountain tour or if we stayed up dancing until a very late hour the previous night. Still, having in mind the number of people who have registered, most of the time you can count on the possibility of using the mentioned locations for dance, even when a big number of people wishes to do some other activities elsewhere.</p>
<p><strong>Other activities:</strong></p>
<p>We can divide the other activities into those coordinated and prepared by us and those which we can recommend for you which are organized by some of the local tourist agencies that offer an extremely broad range of activities such as rafting in the Tara river, different tours (some of which are incredibly exciting, such as the visit to the canyon Nevidio), jeep safari etc.</p>
<p>Activities within the camp which will be coordinated by the organizer:</p>
<ol>
<li>Different activities focused on working on oneself, such as <strong>anti</strong><strong>-</strong><strong>stress and relax programs</strong>, and other activities focused on working on the body, personal expression etc. Like last year, this year we will also have workshops on the subject of <strong>contact improvisation, </strong>and a new activity will be <strong>workshops of modern ballet</strong>. Apart from this we will have <strong>yoga </strong>classes almost every day! All the mentioned activities are free, i.e. they are included in what you pay in the previously mentioned contribution.</li>
<li>This year, like the previous one, we will have workshops of the Argentine folklore dance Chacarera which will be held by Paula Milonguera. She will be at the camp from beginning of August until all the way to the camp&#8217;s end.</li>
<li>Educational tours &#8211; at the moment this means visits to the botanical garden of Kolasin, as well as botanical tours through which you can find out more about the flora of Kolasin. The entrance fee into the botanical garden is a symbolic 1 euro. Apart from these, we also plan to organize one or more visits to the Moraca endowment of Stefan Nemanja which was built in XIIIcentury.</li>
<li>Horseback riding &#8211; there are options of renting horses for an hour or two of riding in the hills nearby, as well as a possibility of organizing day-long tours through the mountains which surround Kolasin. This activity is paid based on the number of horses and the possible hiring of a guide/instructor. In any case, the prices will be significantly cheaper from the regular ones for this type of activities. These activities also depend to a certain extent on the number of horses available at the moment. Signing up for horseback riding is done one or two days before the activity.</li>
<li>Rock climbing &#8211; Very close to Kolasin there is a number of pitches (natural rock formations for climbing). We have people who are experts for this activity, as well as the necessary equipment. A bit of your adventurous spirit is needed <img src="http://www.summertangocamp.com/wp-includes/images/smilies/icon_smile.gif" alt=":)" class="wp-smiley" />  This activity is free. Signing up is necessary one or two days in advance.</li>
<li>Cycling &#8211; The Tourist Organization of Kolasin will provide us with a large number of bikes for an extremely affordable price. The arrangement is that upon taking the bike one leaves 50 cents in the piggy bank <img src="http://www.summertangocamp.com/wp-includes/images/smilies/icon_smile.gif" alt=":)" class="wp-smiley" />  for a ride that will last for up to an hour, while for an entire day of bike riding 1 euro is enough! Some of the organizers can join the group and suggest some interesting route if the need arises.</li>
<li>Smaller mountain tours and field trips (picnics) &#8211; Kolasin is a small town surrounded by numerous mountains and hills. At any point you can decide to go for a shorter or longer visit to the surroundings of Kolasin. In any case, we will occasionally organize shorter, half-day tours and field trips. These activities often take place after a relaxation class in nature, where we simply continue for a walk. Even though a part of the organizers of this event do not eat meat, we will have to satisfy the traditional craving for barbecue :). In these cases most often a part of the camp participants will stay in Kolasin and dance or take part in other activities, while others enjoy the walk.</li>
<li>Bigger mountain tours &#8211; these activities can be dismantled into smaller pieces <img src="http://www.summertangocamp.com/wp-includes/images/smilies/icon_smile.gif" alt=":)" class="wp-smiley" />  Oftentimes one part of those participating in the tour will at some point make camp and enjoy the nature, food and socializing, while others will proceed to some mountain summit or some other more distant destination. Last year&#8217;s field trips to the national park Biogradska Gora, visit to Bjelasica mountain and Komovi mountain have left unforgettable impressions on all who took part. This year we are planning a bigger number of those activities, as well as new destinations. These activities include certain additional expenses related to transport, food &#8211; if barbecue is organized, and possible daily fee for the guide if he/she is needed.</li>
</ol>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>If you play some musical instrument, have a telescope (this is because of last year&#8217;s educational session which lasted until late into the night :) ) or anything similar which can contribute to wealth of activities, please do not hesitate to contribute. So far we have planned some archery (bow and arrow) activities.</p>
<p><strong>Clothing and footwear necessary for the camp</strong></p>
<p>You know what you need for tango <img src="http://www.summertangocamp.com/wp-includes/images/smilies/icon_smile.gif" alt=":)" class="wp-smiley" />  Nights in Kolasin can be quite cool (temperature can fall down to 5 degrees Celsius, most often to 13-14, sometimes even warmer), even though the temperature during the day can go over 30 degrees, which is also a common occurrence. It is good to take this into account. Also, some days can be colder because the mountain weather is occasionally unstable. If rain falls or it gets cold, we will dance more, in a very closed embrace <img src="http://www.summertangocamp.com/wp-includes/images/smilies/icon_smile.gif" alt=":)" class="wp-smiley" /> </p>
<p>Also, field trips and mountain tours require appropriate clothing and footwear. The majority of all tours can be done in regular sneakers, but one part of the activities includes possibilities of climbing to mountain summits and crossing demanding terrain, so it&#8217;s necessary to have adequate mountaineering footwear. We cannot allow those who do not have adequate footwear to join a group which is climbing some more demanding mountain summit! Of course, these activities are optional. For instance, a part of those on the field trip can stay and relax next to a tree and/or barbecue :) while the others will proceed to a mountain summit. It is recommended that you take layers of clothes so that you can adjust yourself to the temperature. Also, you should take, for example, several t-shirts, as during mountain climbing people tend to sweat a lot and it is good to change clothes.</p>
<p><strong>Food and drinks at the </strong><strong>camp</strong></p>
<p>The official restaurant of the tango camp will this year also support this event with extremely low food prices! The price for one meal which includes soup, salad and main course will be only 4,5 euros. You can count that every day there will also be a vegetarian food option in the menu.</p>
<p>Apart from that, within the Spomen dom location there will be a bar open exclusively to the tango camp. You will find both food and drinks there at very affordable prices. The choice of food will depend on the experience on the ground. In any case, you can count on a relatively wide selection of sandwiches etc. Most, if not all accommodation has a kitchen so you can also organize your own food preparation. Bigger tours have the options of either taking your own food with you or making barbecue. In the case of barbecue, there will be previously organized money-gathering so that all the necessary groceries and ingredients are bought at the same time. If you carry your own food, have in mind that in the mountain you can become veeeery hungry, so take care not to underestimate yourself and start begging for food from others <img src="http://www.summertangocamp.com/wp-includes/images/smilies/icon_smile.gif" alt=":)" class="wp-smiley" />  When it comes to water, PLEASE TAKE CARE TO ALWAYS BRING ENOUGH WATER WITH YOU, as there is an important mountain principle of everyone taking care of their own water. We will inform you how much water you should take so that you will have enough of it until the next source of water.</p>
<p>That&#8217;s it for now.</p>
<p>For all additional information you can write to us on : <a href="mailto:tangonaturalmontenegro@gmail.com">tangonaturalmontenegro@gmail.com</a></p>
<p>or ask questions in the Facebook event https://www.facebook.com/events/102048893462130/<br />
or at the Facebook group dedicated to the event: <a href="https://www.facebook.com/groups/215228388600063/">https://www.facebook.com/groups/215228388600063/</a>,<br />
Event website: <a href="http://www.summertangocamp.com/">www.summertangocamp.com</a><br />
Facebook page: <a href="https://www.facebook.com/summertangocamp?fref=ts">https://www.facebook.com/summertangocamp?fref=ts</a></p>
<p>For those who haven&#8217;t done this so far, at the Facebook group of the camp there are photos from last year&#8217;s camp which was wonderful and exciting. These days we will upload some photos that haven&#8217;t seen the light of Facebook so far <img src="http://www.summertangocamp.com/wp-includes/images/smilies/icon_smile.gif" alt=":)" class="wp-smiley" /> </p>
<p>We are very much looking forward to the fun time ahead of us! We feel that after the camp we will become better people and our embraces will be more filled with love and support for the people around us, and our beings will be filled with beautiful and enriching impressions.</p>
<p>Hugs,</p>
<p>TN Team</p>
]]>
</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="karaoke">Karaoke</string>
</resources>
